Hello guys welcome to another video of stock
market friends III Lord General
Insurance Limited has
presented its September quarter financial results.
Today we will analyze it in this video.
Let's start the video friends, the
audited financial statement of the
company is out for the half year and
September quarter and for the second quarter
plus the company has
also declared a final dividend of ₹ per equity share,
whose record date has been kept as 27 October
2023. So now we go to the
financial results of the company and we can see the first console dated
results here,
which are stand alone
results and the numbers are given in lakhs.
If we talk about income, it is ₹49.2
crore, in the last quarter it was ₹4538
crore and in the September 22 quarter the
income is ₹4499 crore, which has
increased in both quarter on quarter and year on year,
after which the expenses, this
time the total expenses
4452 crore, in the previous quarter there was an expense of 4206
crore and in the September 22 quarter there was an
expense of 3988 crore, which means that the
expenses have increased quarter on quarter,
year on year
expenses have also increased
according to the income, but if you
look at the income here, then after which there was a loss in the operating profit, which is the
underwriting profit, here the
company suffered a loss of
1459 crore in underwriting, but this time the
operating profit which has come out is profit
operating profit, which you
can see here, the operating profit is around
597 crore, in the previous quarter it was 331
crore and in the September 22 quarter there is an
operating profit of 510 crore, which has increased quarter on
quarter year on year,
which is the operating profit, but here if
we see this total expense, which is the
non-operating result, we will
see here, then its total expense
which is around  700 sorry expenses have been incurred
of 55.3 crores, negative of 3.2 crores was seen here in the last quarter
and in the September 22 quarter there has been an
expense of 106 crores, after which the
profit of the company came out to be
577 crores net profit, now we will
talk about net profit which is 577 crores,
in the last quarter it was 390 crores and
in the September 22 quarter there is a net
profit of 59.5 crores, there is growth in quarter on quarter
but year on year it is down,
EPS is ₹17, there is
growth in quarter on quarter but year on year it is
down, so guys see the result of the company is
average because there is
growth in quarter on quarter profit but
year on year it is
seen to be down, in profit there was a lot of decline but in operating profit, that
means the non-operating
results saw a slight decline,
but in non-operating results, the
company  Good performance is being
seen, there has been a slight
decline in profit in the last year, so overall the
company has presented decent results here, so
we end the video here,
if you have any doubt, ask in the comment box, we will
meet in the next video, till then bye bye